## Hello

# I'm Suanlianmang

BUNGMUAL, CHURACHANDPUR MANIPUR, INDIA, PO - 795128 +91 7005666024 suanlian.lethil@gmail.com

#### Intro

I am a self-taught developer, who stumbled into programming 7 years ago. I love the problem-solving aspect of programming. It's literally magic to me, creating something out of seemingly nothing.

### Skills

- Fast learner
- Good critical thinking and problem solving
- Good understanding of problems and project requirements
- Great work ethics

\*I don't list any particular technology because I believe once you get the concepts in general, picking up a tech stack isn't that much of an issue. After all the main job of a programmer is to solve a problem, it's just a matter of what tools you used. That being said, I do list the ones I have experience with below

## Other Qualities and Hobbies

- Self proclaim decent writer
- Love challenges and problem-solving
- Highly motivated
- Interest in fields like physics, astronomy, philosophy, psychology, economics, etc. Which I hope to be able to write about one day,
- Loving programming (it was a hobby at first)
- Don't need much supervision

## **Experience**

March 2022 - PRESENT

**1stZoom, Remote** - Python / Django Developer

- Take part in driving solutions and product conceptualization
- Designing database and data models for various integrated applications (Django, Postgres)

- Create a web app with multiple user types (Django, HTML, CSS, JS, AJAX)
- Develop and maintain REST APIs for two applications with token authentications (Django, REST\_framework)
- Modify and improve some web applications (Django)
- Helpout coworkers in so projects

August 2020 - November 2020

### **Sorteddly, Remote** - *Freelancer*

- Discussing and documenting requirements with the client
- Developed and deliver products based on clients' requirements.

## **Education**

May 2018 - May 2021

#### **Don Bosco College, Maram** - BCA

I worked on two web projects with over 90% scores on them during my studies.

### **Awards**

Runner up in 1stZoom hackathon (on services for the restaurant industries) in the first month of work.